appnovation.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Appnovation Technologies Inc.

**Appnovation Technologies, Inc.**  
 **Privacy Policy**

THIS PRIVACY POLICY RELATES TO INFORMATION COLLECTED ON APPNOVATION WEBSITES ACCESSED THROUGH THE URL [APPNOVATION.COM](http://www.appnovation.com/) (collectively, the “Site”).

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Appnovation Technologies, Inc. (“Appnovation,” “we” or “us”) respects the privacy of your information. We provide this explanation about our online information practices as a demonstration of our commitment to protect your privacy.

We do not sell or rent personally-identifying information collected during your use of our Site without your permission.

## The Information We Collect

At the time you register on our Site, we collect and store your name, address, email address and other personally-identifying information. We may also ask you for personally-identifying information at other times, such as if you enter into a promotion, post content to the Site, communicate with us, or complete a survey. If you opt-in to receive a newsletter or other electronic communication, request information regarding an Appnovation or third party product, service, or request a trial version of our products and services, you give us your permission to use your personally-identifying information to provide the information, product, or service that you requested. If the information, product, or service that you requested is provided by or through a third party, including Appnovation contractors and business partners, you give us your permission to share your name and e-mail address and other personally-identifying information reasonably necessary for the third party to provide the information, product, or service that you requested.

In addition, we automatically gather general statistical information about our Site and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, services used, content submitted, etc. We need this information to improve the content and functionality of our Site. We use this information to customize your experience using our Site. We may provide statistical information to third parties, but in doing so we do not reference you by individual name, e-mail address, home address, or telephone number without your permission. We may match user information we collect with offline data available from other sources in order to carry out our services and conduct target advertising and promotions more effectively.

We use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. Some features of our Site may be available only through the use of a cookie. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us who you are and enable us to access your account information so you do not have to re-enter it; gather statistical information about usage by registered or unregistered users, research visiting patterns, and help target advertisements and product offerings based on user interests; and track progress and participation in the Site’s content. In some instances, the third parties appearing at our Site may use their own cookies. Preference and options configurations in your browser determine if and how a cookie will be accepted. You can change those configurations on your computer if you desire. By changing your preferences, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is set, or you can reject all cookies. If you do so and cookies are disabled, you may be required to re-enter your information more often and certain features of our Site may be unavailable.

## The Way We Use Information

We use your personally-identifying information to provide information, products, and services that you have requested, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize our Site’s content, layout, and services.

We may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners, new services promotions, and new product offerings. We may ask you to provide us voluntarily with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests which may be use to customize our service for you.

We use your e-mail address, your mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding administrative notices, marketing promotions, new Appnovation service offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. You can opt out of receiving such contact by sending an email request to [privacy@appnovation.com](mailto:privacy@appnovation.com). This opt-out action is tied directly to an individual email address and not an account or individual. If a visitor uses multiple email addresses at different times at appnovation.com (i.e.: personal and corporate email addresses) it is required that each email address be unsubscribed so that you will not receive further communication from us.

We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or enforce our Terms of Use Agreement. At times, we may review status or activity of multiple users to do so. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to manage our Site and to enhance our Site based on the usage pattern data we receive.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Appnovation will send personally-identifying information about you to other companies or people only when:

  * We need to share your information to provide the information, product, or service you have requested;
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Appnovation, our trusted outside contractors or our partners to provide an Appnovation product or a service or to otherwise assist Appnovation with its business activities. Unless we tell you otherwise, these companies do not have any right to use the personally-identifying information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us and are required to safeguard personally-identifying information and not to disclose personally-identifying information to others;
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; or
  * We need to enforce our Terms of Use Agreement because your actions on our Site violate our Terms of Use Agreement.

## Security

We employ reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. You should note that in using the Appnovation Site, your information will travel through third party infrastructures which are not under our control.

We cannot protect, nor does this Privacy Policy apply to, any text, images, or other information posted on the Site by you or that you voluntarily disclose to other users online through email or the Site’s message boards, blogs, etc. You should never transmit personal or identifying information to other users.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

## How You Can Update, Correct, or Delete Your Information

You have the ability to direct Appnovation to edit, correct or erase your personally-identifying information, at any time. To request such account maintenance, send your email request to [privacy@appnovation.com](mailto:privacy@appnovation.com). You may also indicate that you do not wish to receive messages from Appnovation regarding our services or unsubscribe from Appnovation mailings, send your request to [marketing@appnovation.com](mailto:marketing@appnovation.com). Your information will be changed in Appnovation’s data bases after we receive the information necessary to process your request.

## Children Under 13

We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site, and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a child has provided us with personally-identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

## Third Party Practices

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearing at our Site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer.

## Changes to Our Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our Site at least twenty four (24) hours in advance of its effective date. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the previous Privacy Policy.

## Your Consent

By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.
